uh good afternoon ladies and gentlemen
harali theide from sinic group and today
we have Miss nidi burnwal from ad baa
Sun Life Insurance hello ma'am uh she is
the AP distributor management and now I
would be going through a quick interview
of her so the first question which I
would like to ask her is how was your
overall experience in the India
Insurance Summit and award ceremony maam
so the experience was great uh you
actually get to understand What new
technologies are coming up what new
Solutions especially with generative AI
being in the picture what Creative
Solutions that uh uh the new insure tech
andtech companies are coming up with uh
one of the presentations by uh Deepak uh
from SAS was wonderful it was eye
opening and it gave us a lot of insights
on what can be done in insurance and uh
with data analytics so I think overall
uh very insightful and uh uh thought
generating sessions so yeah thank you
ma'am well said and the next question uh
what would you like to say on your
experience with sinx okay so sinic team
I would say is very proactive uh always
in touch I got reminders follow-ups for
the sessions very well organized uh they
uh got the entire team together through
WhatsApp uh for the panel discussion or
be for uh just the delegates to give
them reminds for the call and I could
see that they're really supporting all
the boots as well uh they're ensuring
that there's enough networking going on
in the event so there's a a value
addition for not just the participants
but also for the uh the companies and
corporates that are participating in the
event so I think very well-managed event
thank you so much ma'am thank you for
being a part and definitely would be
looking forward for you to be one of our
panel members in future as well thank
you for joining in ma'am thank you so
much everyone and now I conclude here
with the interview thank you thank you
ma'am thank you so much